rebellegion.com 2010-05-08

# Rebel Legion Privacy Policy

|   
---  

  |  Rebel Legion Privacy Policy

The Rebel Legion is committed to respecting the privacy of all visitors to our web site. This Privacy Policy explains explains the following things:

  * What kind of information we collect from visitors and members.
  * What we use that information for.
  * Who has access to the information we collect.
  * Our policy on advertising.
  * What to do if you suspect your privacy has been compromised by someone in the Rebel Legion.

_BY USING THIS WEB SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY._ If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, do not use this web site.

## What kind of information do we collect and how do we use it?

### All site visitors

If you visit the Rebel Legion's website, the following information will collected about you:

  * What web browser software you use. Examples include Firefox, Internet Explorer, Konquerer, WebTV, Safari, etc.
  * What operating system your computer uses. Examples include Windows XP, Apple OS X, Linux, Solaris, etc.
  * How you got to our website. For example, if you found a link to our site from another website, then we will know which website linked to us. If you came here from a search engine, such as Google, we will know what words you used in your search.
  * The date, time, and length of your visit here.
  * Any website errors you may have encountered.

This information is collected so that we can understand how people are reaching our site, what parts of the site are most popular, and how best to tailor the site to suit our visitors. This information is not made available to anyone except the Legion webmaster, the Legion Council, and the Base and Outpost commanders. In practice, it is unlikely that anyone but the Legion webmaster will understand or care about the above information.

### Registered forum users

If you sign up to post on our discussion forums, the only information required from you is your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is used for the following purposes:

  * To send you your username and password so you can login and post on the forum.
  * To allow you to retrieve your username and password in case you forget it.
  * To alert you via e-mail of any technical problems that may affect you, such as increases in security that require you to login again.
  * For the webmaster to contact you regarding technical problems with your account.
  * If you are banned due to misbehavior on our forums, you will receive an e-mail detailing the length of punishment and reasons for it.

You can control who has access to your e-mail address at any time by editing your profile. You may also enter information about your location including country, zip/postal code and as well as what time zone you live in. This information is used to correctly display the local time on the forums and news pages. You may also enter your name, your favorite and least favorite Star Wars movies and characters, your gender, date of birth, Instant Messenger info, website address, and other personal information. This information is viewable to all but is not used for anything other than statistics.

### Legion Members

Members off the Legion, (please see the Club Charter for information about what a member is) are required to provide a great deal more information than ordinary users. Here is what is required:

  * Your country and zip/postal code. This is required so that we know which Base or Outpost you belong to as a member.
  * A photograph of you in your costume. Since this is a costume-oriented club, we must have a photo to verify that you have an appropriate costume and we will be posting this photo on the website under your profile.

In addition to the optional information that you can enter as a forum user, you may enter your telephone number and/or mailing address. Like your e-mail address, you can choose to limit who has access to this information. If you want, everyone who views your profile can see this information, or you can restrict it to members only or staff only. The default setting is to restrict the information to Legion staff members only.

## Advertising

The Rebel Legion does not use any form of advertising on the website beyond linking to relevant Star Wars and Science-Fiction websites in our Links page. We also do not permit users to use our forum, private message system, chat room, or other areas of our website for the purpose of advertising and/or SPAM.

If you have experienced internet advertising such as banners, pop-ups, pop-unders or other ads while visiting our site, then this is because your computer has ad-ware or spyware (collectively known as scumware) installed on your computer. Tools such as [Ad-Aware](http://www.lavasoft.com/ "Visit LavaSoft's home page and download Ad-Aware"), [Spybot Search and Destroy](http://www.spybot.info/ "Jump to the homepage for SpyBot Search and Destroy"), and [Spyware Blaster](http://www.javacoolsoftware.com/spywareblaster.html "Go to the website for Spyware Blaster") can help remove such software from your computer.

## What to do if you suspect someone in the Legion has compromised your privacy

If you believe that someone within the Legion who has access to your contact information, the first thing that you should do is check the privacy settings for your e-mail address and other contact info. If it is set to "Everyone" or "Members only," then you may want to restrict to staff members. Next you should gather all details and information you have and e-mail the Legion with that information. Here is some information to include in your message:

  * Your username and/or real name
  * If you have any idea who has violated your trust, please state who and why you think they did it
  * When was your private information exposed and how or where did it happen?
  * What the privacy setting on your information was set to at the time your information was exposed

|
